<resources>
    <string name="app_name">directSmsCall_compose</string>
    <string name="permissionRequired">Required permission</string>
    <string name="permissionSettings">Settings</string>
    <string name="permissionGranted">Granted permission</string>
    <string name="permissionDenied">Denied permission</string>
    <string name="permissionPermDenied">Go Settings</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="contactsPermissionInfo">Contact access</string>
    <string name="contactsPermissionNeeded">We need contacts permission to contact them</string>
    <string name="contactsPermissionDenied">You denied contacts permission, please enable this permission to enjoy this app.</string>
    <string name="contactsPermissionGranted">You have given access to contacts. Thanks!</string>
    <string name="contactsPermissionPermanentDenied">You permanently denied contacts permission, please enable this permission in your settings to enjoy this app.</string>
    <string name="contactsPermissionsReady">Contacts permission ready</string>
    <string name="cameraPermissionInfo">Camera access</string>
    <string name="cameraPermissionNeeded">We need camera permission to take photos</string>
    <string name="cameraPermissionDenied">You denied camera permission, please enable this permission to enjoy this app.</string>
    <string name="cameraPermissionGranted">You have given access to camera. Thanks!</string>
    <string name="cameraPermissionPermanentDenied">You permanently denied camera permission, please enable this permission in your settings to enjoy this app.</string>
    <string name="cameraPermissionsReady">Camera permission ready</string>
    <string name="writeExternalStoragePermissionInfo">Write external access</string>
    <string name="writeExternalStoragePermissionNeeded">We need write external storage permission to save your pictures</string>
    <string name="writeExternalStoragePermissionDenied">You denied write external storage permission, please enable this permission to enjoy this app.</string>
    <string name="writeExternalStoragePermissionGranted">You have given access to write external storage. Thanks!</string>
    <string name="writeExternalStoragePermissionPermanentDenied">You permanently denied write external storage permission, please enable this permission in your settings to enjoy this app.</string>
    <string name="writeExternalStoragePermissionReady">External storage write permission ready</string>
    <string name="readExternalStoragePermissionInfo">Read External access</string>
    <string name="readExternalStoragePermissionNeeded">We need storage read permission to show your pictures</string>
    <string name="readExternalStoragePermissionDenied">You denied read external storage permission, please enable this permission to enjoy this app.</string>
    <string name="readExternalStoragePermissionGranted">You have given access to read external storage. Thanks!</string>
    <string name="readExternalStoragePermissionPermanentDenied">You permanently denied read external storage permission, please enable this permission in your settings to enjoy this app.</string>
    <string name="readExternalStoragePermissionReady">Read external storage permission ready</string>
    <string name="manageExternalStoragePermissionInfo">Manage External Storage access</string>
    <string name="manageExternalStoragePermissionNeeded">We need manage external storage permission to show your pictures</string>
    <string name="manageExternalStoragePermissionDenied">You denied manage external storage permission, please enable this permission to enjoy this app.</string>
    <string name="manageExternalStoragePermissionGranted">You have given manage external storage permission. Thanks!</string>
    <string name="manageExternalStoragePermissionPermanentDenied">You permanently denied manage external storage permission, please enable this permission in your settings to enjoy this app.</string>
    <string name="manageExternalStorageAccessReady">Manage external storage permission ready</string>
    <string name="locationPermissionInfo">Location Access</string>
    <string name="locationPermissionNeeded">We need access to your location to know where you are</string>
    <string name="locationPermissionDenied">You denied location permission, please enable this permission to enjoy this app.</string>
    <string name="locationPermissionGranted">You have given access to your location. Thanks!</string>
    <string name="locationPermissionPermanentDenied">You permanently denied access to your location, please enable this permission in your settings to enjoy this app.</string>
    <string name="locationPermissionReady">Location ready</string>
    <string name="smsPermissionInfo">SMS Access</string>
    <string name="smsPermissionNeeded">We need SMS permission to send SMS messages</string>
    <string name="smsPermissionDenied">You denied SMS permission, please enable this permission to enjoy this app.</string>
    <string name="smsPermissionGranted">You have given access to send SMS. Thanks!</string>
    <string name="smsPermissionPermanentDenied">You permanently denied SMS permission, please enable this permission in your settings to enjoy this app.</string>
    <string name="smsPermissionReady">SMS permission ready</string>
    <string name="callPermissionInfo">Call Access</string>
    <string name="callPermissionNeeded">We need phone permission to make calls</string>
    <string name="callPermissionDenied">You denied phone call permission, please enable this permission to enjoy this app.</string>
    <string name="callPermissionGranted">You have given access to phone call. Thanks!</string>
    <string name="callPermissionPermanentDenied">You permanently denied Phone call permission, please enable this permission in your settings to enjoy this app.</string>
    <string name="callPermissionReady">Phone call permission ready</string>
</resources>